goodlifeeats.com 2019-07-01

# Privacy Policy | Good Life Eats

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you what personally identifiable information we may collect and how it may be used. This statement only applies to this Website.

Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

 **Good Life Eats found at https://www.goodlifeeats.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).  The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion. This policy is effective from date 5/4/2018.**

 _If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of GoodLife Eats then you may[contact](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/) Good Life Eats._

#### What We Collect

Information You Voluntarily Submit to the Website: We may collect personal information from you such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting a contact form.

 **Information We Collect from Others** : We may receive information about you from other sources.  You may link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts to your profile when leaving a comment.  If you choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and/or Google accounts, we may receive your name, email address and profile picture associated with that account.

 **Automatically-Collected Information** : We automatically collect certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website. For example, when you use the Website, we will log your IP address, operating system type, browser type, referring website, pages you viewed, and the dates/times when you accessed the Website. We may also collect information about actions you take when using the Website, such as links clicked.

 **Cookies** : We may log information using cookies, which are small data files stored on your browser by the Website. We may use both session cookies, which expire when you close your browser, and persistent cookies, which stay on your browser until deleted, to provide you with a more personalized experience on the Website.

### What we do with the information we gather

  * We may use the information collected in the following ways:
  * To operate and maintain the Website;
  * To identify you as a user of the Website;
  * To send you promotional information, such as newsletters. Each email promotion will provide information on how to opt-out of future mailings;
  * To send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * To respond to your comments or inquiries;
  * To provide you with user support;
  * To track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity.

#### THIRD-PARTY USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may share your information with third parties when you explicitly authorize us to share your information.

Additionally, the Website may use third-party service providers to service various aspects of the Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies.

The Website currently uses the following third-party service providers:

 **Google Analytics** – this service tracks Website usage and provides information such as referring websites and user actions on the Website. Google Analytics may capture your IP address, but no other personal information is captured by Google Analytics.

 **Feedblitz** – this service is used for delivery of email updates and newsletters. We store your name and email address for purposes of delivering such communications.  Please refer to Feedblitz’s privacy policy for further information.

 _This list may be amended from time to time in the Website’s sole discretion._

Except when required by law, we will not sell, distribute, or reveal your email addresses or other personal information without your consent.

However, we may disclose or transfer personal information collected through the Website to third parties who acquire all or a portion of our business, which may be the result of a merger, consolidation, or purchase of all or a portion of our assets, or in connection with any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding brought by or against us.

#### ANONYMOUS DATA

From time to time, we may use anonymous data, which does not identify you alone, or when combined with data from other parties. This type of anonymous data may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Examples of this anonymous data may include analytics or information collected from cookies.

#### PUBLICLY VISIBLE INFORMATION

If you create a user profile on the Website or leave a comment, certain information may be publicly visible.  To create a user profile, you must choose a username and password and input your email address for profile confirmation.  Your email address will never be available publicly.  At your option, you may also add an avatar, a profile description, and a link to your website.

You may also choose to link your Facebook, Instagram, and Google Account.

Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and website information.

#### COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

The Website uses cookies to store visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, customize Website content based on visitors’ browser type or other information that the visitor sends. Cookies may also be used by third-party services, such as Google Analytics, as described herein.

Users may, at any time, prevent the setting of cookies, by the Website, by using a corresponding setting of your internet browser and may thus permanently deny the setting of cookies.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you may choose to modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. However, if users deactivate the setting of cookies in your Internet browser, not all functions of our Website may be entirely usable.

#### ADVERTISING

### Display Ads

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve content and advertisements when you visit the Website, which may use cookies, as noted above.

### Retargeting Ads

From time to time, the Website may engage in remarketing efforts with third-party companies, such as Google, Facebook, or Instagram, in order to market the Website. These companies use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s past visits to the Website.

### Affiliate Program Participation

The Website may engage in affiliate marketing, which is done by embedding tracking links into the Website. If you click on a link for an affiliate partnership, a cookie will be placed on your browser to track any sales for purposes of commissions.

Good Life Eats is a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn advertising fees by advertising and links to Amazon.com.

As part of this Amazon Associates program, the Website will post customized links, provided by Amazon, to track the referrals to their website. This program utilizes cookies to track visits for the purposes of assigning commission on these sales.

### Newsletters

On the Website, you may subscribe to our newsletter, which may be used for advertising purposes. All newsletters sent may contain tracking pixels.

The pixel is embedded in emails and allows an analysis of the success of online marketing campaigns. Because of these tracking pixels, we may see if and when you open an email and which links within the email you click.

Also, this allows the Website to adapt the content of future newsletters to the interests of the user. This behavior will not be passed on to third parties.

#### Your Rights

 **Opt-out** – You may opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also [notify us](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/) to be removed from our mailing list.

 **Access** – You may access the personal information we have about you by [submitting a request via our contact form](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/).

 **Amend** – You may [contact us](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/) to amend or update your personal information.

 **Forget** – In certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, [please submit a request](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/)

 _Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes or to complete transactions, or when required by law._

#### SENSITIVE INFORMATION

### Your Personal Information

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the Website. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

#### CHILDREN’S INFORMATION

The Website does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, [please contact us immediately](https://www.goodlifeeats.com/contact/) and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest.

However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.

You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### CONTACT INFORMATION

At any time, please contact us for questions related to this Privacy Policy.
